imagine a world where you no longer have
to work where there is no need to Trey
the best hours of your day and the best
years of your life to make ends meet a
future where we as a society have
figured out how to meet all of our needs
and most of our wants we have all have
healthy organic food homes that are
beautiful and safe and communities we
live in we have as big of a wardrobe as
you would want to have designed
specifically for you your style and your
body type or we all have access to the
knowledge of all of humankind in an
organized and easily usable way so we
can use that knowledge to create
solutions for ourselves or communities
in the world or we can contribute in
other ways allowing others to do that
work we can spend our days creating art
playing sports being in nature going to
concerts doing things that we love with
people we love where we have access to
education tailored to your learning
style so that you're able to learn
anything in the most efficient manner
possible we're able to communicate and
collaborate with anyone on the planet
regardless of language barrier or
distance we have a global government
that we all run together through liquid
democracy and you can be as an
individual involved yours hands off as
you want to be because all the
information that is used to make
decisions is open and transparent
available to everyone to solve problems
and vote on solutions so we are
continually improving this somewhat
utopian idea of the future requires the
current system to not be there a
collapse of the system is scary it is
chaotic potentially violent and deadly
too many those in power to fight against
it for obvious reasons but what if we
were able to create a wonderful and
sustainable future peacefully if we were
able to continue our current society and
our lives and figure it and do what's
working
well we build a new system underneath
like scaffolding as we're able to design
and employ better solutions the old
systems naturally fall away peacefully
we don't start from zero after societal
collapse you don't let our society
collapse and we don't just continue as
if there's no problem or somebody else
will solve it together we organize and
figure out where we are what is working
and what is not working create solutions
that improve our world without
government involvement without
capitalism or minimize capitalism and
propping up the problems that we're
trying to fix in the first place we
create an online platform that enable us
to organize and collaborate designed
specifically for that where we can solve
the inefficiencies in our systems and
create solutions that work a platform
that walks us through the steps from
discovering what the problem is
discussing the problem the knowledge
that's needed to implement solutions
implementing those solutions and ongoing
monitoring to see if it's working and to
improve the system a space to go and
spend our time feeling connected and
then what we are doing actually matters
and is having an effect where we can
leave energized instead of drained a
place where you can come together and be
the change that you want to see in the
world I'm Pinterest on steroids
organization owned by all of us that is
run cooperatively with democracy and
transparency crowd funded and
crowd-sourced ideas that build on each
other and work together an organized web
of doing if this speaks to you if you
want to help co-create a better future I
first grade in a way to collaborate
online please contact me or join the
facebook facebook group for updates
crowd democracy the links will be in the
description for this video together we
can create a new world 7
Lee and strong